(Mrs Cooper:)All right, Penny, your turn.
Okay, um, ahem. Hey, God. What's up?
Um. I'm good, but it would be a big help
to my family...
(Penny:)...if you could get my brother
to stop cooking meth.
(Penny:)But no cops. Be cool.
(Mrs Cooper:)She also goes a little overboard
on the "Iove thy neighbor."
(Mrs Cooper:)Could probably use that chat
you had with Mary Magdalene.
(Mrs Cooper:)Leonard, you're up.
Wasserman, you're on deck.
(Leonard:)Okay. I don't know.
(Leonard:)It's probably a little late to ask you
to make me taller.
(Leonard:)Oh, um...
If you could help out with my girIfriend.
She's all the way in lndia.
(Leonard:)- That would be great.
- Hear that? Girl trouble.
(Mrs Cooper:)Turns out we were both wrong
on that front.
(Mrs Cooper:)- How about you?
- Uh, me? No. Thanks, I'm good.
(Howard:)I'm really just trying not to burst
into flames. Heh.